Hello.
Okay, well, you know, this is kind of cool.
Like I can, oh my gosh, you see my green screen and stuff.
I can put it on here.
I'm just testing out how this will look.
Can share my screen on here,
but I'll still kind of do edit.
Okay, customization.
I can add a trailer let me see I'll add I'll add this one
Trouble saving my video we try in five seconds. Hi guys. Oh
Sorry, we cannot update your video
Where is the fricking
There should be a way to put up with them put up a
Okay
Jada, hello, let me see so I can't put these stuff up on the screen right now
I'm just trying to see the different things last time. I was on here. I was able to do some stuff like um
Like change the like use the green screen and stuff. I don't know where it is. Oh, hold on. Maybe some of the site
Channel level pop-up dashboard. Okay. Here we go
Let's see
So they add
Okay, well so far I've been able to add ads here
Engages my audience and see I can do a poll
Okay, we're listening to questions and answers from the chat
As you can ask tarot questions you can ask questions about me. We'll just do a little fun Q&A. There's not going to be a
a
What's it called a?
Panel right now because we're not I can't do panels on this channel, but
someone wants to someone does want to
contribute
And sponsor a panel I will end and start a panel on the other channel
Hang on the channel. Okay. We know the aliens arrive. Hmm. Okay. Are they already here?
I think if they have if there's a possibility of the aliens coming they've already been here
Maybe they already left a long time ago. Maybe they're not coming back. So, um
But I think if they've been here they if they are around they have already been here. It's my favorite food
Oh, I like comfort food. I like, um, I love I love bagels and cream cheese. I like macaroni and cheese
I like uh, I like all kinds of other flaminion my favorite steak. I think nice Cabernet Sauvignon
Yeah
So that's that one. Okay
Yeah, I'm having fun doing if you anyone wants to ask some questions to what they send you in the delivery this time
It was a couple of things from grubhub and she said her door dash or something like that
She had a couple things. She's like, well, I don't know what to do with the food
I was like, well, I'd say I think you had to keep it. She's like I'd rather have the cash or something like that and then
then she left and
What she said, oh well they called and they said our thank you for like bringing it and I said what's the name and she's like
She told me the number. Who's my celebrity crush?
Like being a celebrity kind of like makes you less attractive to me
I don't really like maybe Tommy Lee or something like that because he's like kind of kind of cute
But it's like when you're select becoming a celebrity almost becomes like too
Too popular or something for me. I don't know
The J-Dog sent me penis pictures
He sent me a picture of him on the on the massage table on a he went to rub one onto this rub maps plays
And he sent me a picture. He's like based down on the massage table
That was what he sent me. It was great. I'm just kidding
Oh, hi, baby.
Oh.
Yeah.
So I'm looking forward to the 25th.
So I'm going to say, why do you let people
like J-Dogg abuse your panelists who talk crap
about people he doesn't like?
Well, a lot of people will do that.
And that's like, I don't necessarily know the truth
about the situations or whatever.
I do let people talk and, you know,
I like people when they respond and everything.
Let me see.
Fly settings to streams created by third party
tools, monetization on overlay.
These default overlays say, OK, there's some default.
Uh-oh.
Uses URL to add overlay to my encoder.
Oh, OK.
I don't know how this works.
Would I make out a Saman?
I kind of like the gap in the teeth, you know?
I like a gap in the teeth and it's like,
so that's kind of cute, but it's like, I don't know.
He's probably going, he's like so goofy.
I don't know if I would, if I'm really attracted,
he just start laughing the whole time in it.
Maybe I would laugh, if I was laughing along with it,
that'd be fun, but if he was just like,
trying to press me the whole time,
I'd be like, I would lose interest pretty quickly, I think.
Oh, do you guys hear me by the way?
Okay, hold on, is this, is this thing on?
I wonder if this microphone is right, okay.
Channel level settings pop out dashboard. I don't have access to these features. Okay
Yeah, last time I was on here. I was able to do other stuff like oh here
Moderation activity. I want to see that. Yeah, okay
Okay, I got this Q&A thing up
with the moderation activity
do I enjoy being a low cow? I don't think I am. Hold on. You know what I enjoy? I enjoy
having this immediate hiding. I'm like right here. So I love that. But yeah, I don't consider
myself a low cow, but I do know a lot of low cow farmers and it's like, you know, if they
Not pretty interesting for them, right black walnut another. This is another one of
AMC that's one another one of his alts
Allied master computer, okay, so but I'm able to that's another because it's one of the positive things about right now. I'm able to
Take that off. Okay, so let's see. I still don't know why I'm not able to...
Anyway, yeah, those are pretty interesting stories. Yeah, I don't know. I could ask Tony that.
Tony knows what it's like to be a little cow because he's been one for years.
Are you gonna feel bad when Alexandra turns on you?
Okay, so I don't think she will.
So lovely lady, let me see.
So you don't like J-Dog or Alexandra
and you're asking about the delivery.
So who are you lovely lady?
Not a mod.
I don't think she will.
But of course people are gonna, they always say,
Stuff about people, you know everybody especially when there's a friendship, right? I'm missing myself like any of that, right?
How many gallons of lube?
Zero I don't have gallons. I don't have the gallon containers of lube. I
Get it by the by the court. I've like the several several hundred courts
The gallons too heavy heavy for me to carry upstairs myself
Okay, let's see 9.50. Oh, it's home. I've been out tonight. Let's see
What else can I do here? I can share my screen. That's kind of cool. Okay, but I don't want to like
Can show you some of my new
Many shorts
You're my channel, shorts.
Yeah, you can eat my shorts.
Okay, shorts?
Oh, I only put one up.
Okay, well, we can have a look.
Clicks my stream just feeds the fire in this mystic weed
Oh, I tell you, okay, yeah, let's, oh, okay, oh, really, okay, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Alexander, did she have you blocked?
Hey, let's join together.
Have you fucking nuts, dude?
She be like so overwhelmed, you're like, what the fuck is this, like, what is this, yeah?
Let's go together.
Let's fucking, let's just fuck that shit up.
Okay
Oh, I tell you I play since I was 11, but I'm now retarded and he's an adult. Okay
No, you don't have free speech because it's my speech. It's making enemies out of this person. You're twice this ass
For Jim jams
Okay
I don't know guys. I'm gonna try to bring more people up in a second because I don't when I'm like go from a joke
Yeah, I like this right here
I want to lick that off of you, my God.
He wants to lick it.
He's going to kiss it.
He's doing it with a full chin strap.
I don't know who I'm going to put.
A full Amish chin strap.
We're an Amish person.
That's all I know.
Like an Amish man with a full chin strap.
No, a chin strap.
Turns to a full goatee when he pulls out his pants a little bit.
I need to know you.
If I know you, I'll add you to the show.
But if I don't know you, I have to wait a little bit, OK?
And then can you put like a, like a, like a little mustache, like a, like a retard that can't grow mustache, like kind of can, like a little bit.
I was about to say, yeah, okay, make it blackfish.
Can I see your nipples showing up?
Can you make like, you make antennas with the nipples and like attach them to your nipples, like with antennas?
Okay, okay, I'll wait
I don't know guys. I'm gonna try to bring more people up in a second. I cuz I don't when I'm like
Where did you meet her the methadone miles
I didn't mean to make a horse in the lake. Why are you my discord? I know I know the song
I know I know Howard Stern. I know the song
I know I know every like racist redneck fucking song in the world. Okay guys, you're not gonna fool me
I knew that song instantly. I've heard that song. Okay. I even might have laughed one the time
We're twice with the song. There's no
Not approved for my show, okay?
So everyone that's saying to let him up
because you're trying to get me in trouble and stuff,
I'm gonna be, you're in trouble for like 24 hours, okay?
I'm not trying to get you in trouble.
Okay
Yeah, Jamie you co-wrote that song. I'm gonna say you core that song you should only let people on you know and people
Great song. Why I know that now what now I will tonight tonight. It's a special. It's made it's a VIP only did he part?
I'm not afraid of your motherfuckin' chassas kick, Jimmy.
That's- that's-
You- alright, you go ahead, Paul.
Okay, I'm all- I'm all- I'm like-
Okay, wait in front of the reason I'm not having backwine shows
is because I'm making unfounded accusations against me.
You fucking racist.
Lippy lips. Lippy lips.
You cheated on me with psyche.
Oh, cool.
We should all do a dance together. Does anybody know any dance songs?
We need music.
He was involved too.
He was fucking there too.
We can't dance to fucking air.
You're a gypsy. You'll just dance to anything.
Shut up.
I could I could get a fucking a little like a
Symbols or any type of fucking something that jingles and you'll dance with those
Chimes like a one like a one time
I can't see your face. I feel like throwing up. I can't see Jen's face
Okay, I'll post a song and the Joker can you play a song I'll post it's a dance song right?
I don't know if everyone like it or not
My song or Joker song Jamie. I mean we all know okay. Well every song never mind
It just pick a song. Jamie really likes the thong-fong. You cheated on me. It would psych you
I'm gonna slap it real hard. You gonna sit up there and see what happens when we put it inside. You did
He was embarrassed. He didn't want everybody to know what he showed you know, it's not stripes person
I thought I'm so used to Persian dick when I saw Bronzeboro's dick. I was like wow
I did not know I took a screenshot. I see your heart and I see I see a good heart and everybody
Yeah, I wish I could see chat for you. Okay. Let me okay. I'll get them in
Crystal sandwich
Honestly, I don't know what happened today I
cleaning. I've got some real life stuff done, you know, like so I missed all your guys and stuff,
but I will say, of everybody's panels, your panel is the best. And people, because
I really feel like everybody is, uh, able to join here.
You know, even the homies that, uh, that, uh, we like each other, like, for, for instance, and thank you.
We have, like, we have, like, love for each other, because people don't understand this.
We know we're all, we know we're all crazy at the end of the day.
You know these people that are taken advantage of
Like that KK woman that step into a realm
You're talking about interdimensional beings and to this current day and I have learned to transmute and choose to
There is that's that's why science. I know
me dizzy
Let's see. It's just kind of cool. Let me see. I don't understand why. Oh, yeah. Well, I guess I will still see their messages
Hopefully no one else will
Know what I am okay
Okay, thank you 31 people in the chat. Wow
I mean look at the dashboard one more time
Okay, let's see what I can do here. Okay 87 views. Okay
Guys you see an ad if I do this
Try again, it says
Okay, no nevermind. Okay, I guess you know, okay. Well, I
See when you put your videos into opus you put the entire hour long video in or do you bring in a smaller clips with the interesting parts?
that the particular program I'm using right now is
It does 45 minutes at a time. It's not Opus Clips. It's a different one. It's called CLAP, K-L-A-P, and
It does 45 minutes at a time. You can only have a three hours or shorter video
to put in there
and then it yeah, and so I
Tried to like just find where there's guests and stuff like and then put it during that part
But I didn't do one video where it was all me and that's not very good, but there's a limited number of videos I can do right now.
I can also go to StreamYard and I can make clips of like the last show. I can put those on immediately actually.
Let me see if I can do that. StreamYard and I can go to Library and then you go to the video, open the video and you can go Generate.
It's generating clips for me.
And then we see yeah, I don't know if I can do this one. Yeah, well this one. Yeah, I published it, but it was all
They clipped the clips so it has the same basically out the same busy AI that picks out the clips
Is like the same one because it picks up the same clips and stuff
But it has to be for two hours
See hi, okay
Yeah, I know a lecture. There's like six six. There's just there's still like few videos like better like the better like listen to
And I'm just been making kind of fast. I do like some of the but I can pick out some of the clips
I mean, yeah, those weren't that great. I know but uh
And some of them are pretty embarrassing, but I mean, it's like I think they've been like looked at for virality and stuff
I don't I don't know I try my best I try my best to find to put an interesting part
Very limited you see okay
So I either
Someone someone donates $10. I will do three readings one for you and then two people that you choose and then
And I will move over to the stream yard and then I'll open a panel after that or I'll just open a panel
I don't have my ability to put anything on the screen right now, so someone could put
my cash app, dollar sign, Psyche Awakens, and otherwise we can watch some stuff here.
bit shoot, yeah, oh, one second
Everyone wants a pair.
My friends laughed when I said I'd found shoes.
By asking your help, in the tremendous task of informing and alerting the American people.
What we are opposed around the world, by a monolithic and ruthless conspiracy, have
They're all around the world. They're all the power they need.
That's the point.
They're young dogs.
They said young dogs could be anybody's chip.
That's all the whole society.
Thank you
I'm just having a laugh till I'm in a monster cross my hand
Hey, you got that
I don't see my hat today
You get your little one of two ways
What's it gonna fit me?
Who's it gonna fit me?
Okay, thank you so much
I just, it's not coming on my screen.
Or like, I just see, like, the problem.
Well, I've only seen the questions.
I've only seen the questions.
that was irreversible. This was not an election. This was a revolution. This was irregular warfare
at its finest. We have what we call citizen journalists. We have an army of digital soldiers.
You're here because you've made a decision about something in your life. You can't sit back.
You have responsibility. We must. You have to have to fight this country. Okay, I'll do it right now.
I don't like this.
I think somebody's gonna come to you with something you want and you got something they want
I think if you share your shelter they can share their fire something like that
Okay, this is for the collective by the way, so you might resonate everybody here might resonate
I mean after this reading I'll go to my other other stream your stuff. This is dismay. Okay
Disappointed about something and maybe like some maybe that it's not gonna work out as well as we thought or maybe or maybe we have had
Somebody to come in and we thought it would be great and it's like instead of like, you know warming us
They burned down the house something like that. Okay, you gotta watch you let into your private space
You know we have the survivor, but you're gonna learn lessons from this and become stronger. Also, you're gonna survive this experience, okay?
The survivor you see you see see land ahead, you know, even though you've been in the water you see like there's hope. Okay, there's
don't
Fred okay, we also have morning
Okay, if you're a survivor, I don't know it's like if you're a survivor and then you know
You'll be able to mourn for the other people that didn't survive
Something similar
Or somebody not everyone's gonna make it. We also have flood, you know, like I keep hearing about the 23rd
I don't know if there's gonna be some something happening at 23rd, but there might be some kind of flood
It's gonna be a flood of emotion too. This could be a lot of emotion coming to you once water represents emotions
So we do have some kind of
surge of these you know violent maybe violent motions it feels like everything's
going underwater they also have the joy ride but maybe you'll have fun you'll
like enjoy this instead of like you know being scared maybe just enjoy the ride
also this could be some kind of like spirit the talking to you spirit or
entity communicating with you okay what else we got
This one says be gone. This is like, you know
Getting something out right if you've got this entity
I think that a joy riding on you you need to you need to get him a get him off you
You can say be gone. You can do banishing rituals. Okay
You know another heli Helen like Helen of Troy
We also have accusations, okay
There might be a lot of finger pointing after this.
You know, oh, you do this, you do this, you do something.
Don't feel like you did something wrong.
I think that you're just trying to get the demons out of it,
or, and then also the lobby.
Okay, so this is kind of feeling naked.
Like maybe like a bad dream going to the middle
of your hotel lobby, you open the door,
you're naked inside the hotel lobby.
What's the advice for everybody?
Let's get some advice.
This one says hysterics. I think just like laugh just like it's like no matter what I just enjoyed enjoy the
Enjoy the show or the cops in my house. No, they're not. It's the the gardeners
I'm gonna show my door but guys that was that reading but I'm gonna go back to my stream yard
So let's meet me over in my stream yard and like one right now. Okay, I'm right back. Okay
Well, thank you for the donation to I love you